The foam inside this shoe is like
nothing I've ever seen, and I'm testing
them out. Okay, so in your running shoe,
you have the upper piece, which
comfortably holds your foot, the
outsole, which hits the ground, and the
midsole, which determines, every time
your foot hits the ground, how much
energy you get back. That's energy
return. A normal energy return is about
60%, but this shoe, independent studies
are showing
74%. Can you see those bumps? That's
because of the way it's made, with
special beads like this. For years, in
order to make a shoe this bouncy, you
needed to put a stiff carbon fiber plate
[music] inside, which is great for
energy return on race day. But in your
everyday runs, it can be a little
punishing. But this shoe
doesn't need it. And it's still all
based in performance and grounded in
race innovation for all this energy
return. If you want to try them with me,
search for Adidas Hyperboost or go to
this link.